The Flutter CLI developer tool uses Google Analytics to report usage and diagnostic
data along with package dependencies, and crash reporting to send basic crash
reports. This data is used to help improve the Dart platform, Flutter framework,
and related tools.

Telemetry is not sent on the very first run. To disable reporting of telemetry,
run this terminal command:

    flutter --disable-analytics

If you opt out of telemetry, an opt-out event will be sent, and then no further
information will be sent. This data is collected in accordance with the Google
Privacy Policy (https://policies.google.com/privacy).

Please note that analytics reporting was already disabled, and will continue to be disabled.

